Preliminary Guide to the Richard Irvin & Co. Records circa 1824-1939 (bulk, 1860s-1919) MS 324
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Bound volumes, circa 1848-1914
  - Exchange Account. Monthly Statement (2), 1864 July (Volume SN-360)
  - Mechanics' National Bank. Checks (32) (Volume SN-361)
  - Mechanics' National Bank. Checks (35) (Volume SN-362)
  - Mechanics' National Bank. Checks (37) (Volume SN-363)
  - Mechanics' National Bank. Checks 1,801 to 3,000 (Volume SN-364)
  - Mechanics' National Bank. Checks (Volume SN-365)
  - Mechanics' National Bank. Checks 4,20[1?] to 5,4[00?] (Volume SN-366)
  - Brick [Bright?] (Volume SN-367)
  - [Mechanics' National Bank?] Checks 12,601 to 13,800 (Volume SN-368)
  - [Mechanics' National Bank?] [Checks?] (34) (Volume SN-369)
  - Mechanics' National Bank. Checks 901 to 1,800 (Volume SN-370)
  - Mechanics' National Bank. Checks (Volume SN-371)
  - [Mechanics' National Bank?] Checks 13,801 to 15,000 (Volume SN-372)
  - Mechanics' National Bank. Checks 5,401 to 6,600 (Volume SN-373)
  - [contents unknown] (Volume SN-374)
  - Checks (41). Mechanics' National Bank (Volume SN-375)
  - National Bank of State of New York. Checks (42?) (Volume SN-376)
  - Mechanics' National Bank. Checks (45) (Volume SN-377)
  - [contents unknown] (Volume SN-378)
  - [Mechanics' National Bank?] [Checks?] (36) (Volume SN-379)
  - Mechanics' National Bank. Checks (47) (Volume SN-380)
  - Mechanics' National Bank. Checks (49) (Volume SN-381)
  - American Exchange / National Bank. Checks 9,001 to 10,200 (Volume SN-382)
  - Mechanics' National Bank. Checks (46) (Volume SN-383)
  - [? Merchant?], 1862 November - 1867 (Volume SN-384)
  - [contents unknown] (Volume SN-385)
  - [contents unknown] (Volume SN-386)
  - [manila file + bundle] (Volume SN-387)
  - American School of Opera. Checks. Richard Irvin Jr., Treasurer (Volume SN-388)
  - Transfers (Volume SN-389)
  - Certificates of Stock (Volume SN-390)
  - Bonds (Volume SN-391)
  - Drafts (Volume SN-392)
  - Transfers 1 to 500 (Volume SN-393)
  - Bonds (Volume SN-394)